The city sleeps in shades of grey Another dawn
begins, another street, another day When no one
ever wins, a hollow echo in the square A promise
whispered low, of somewhere else, beyond
compare A place where true things grow The faces
blur, a passing stream A river deep and wide Lost
in a half-forgoing dream Where do the lost ones
hide? Do you hear I? A whisper on the wind, a
melody so clear Oh, the true light gleams
Will you come back to where the true light gleams
And home is always near
We chase the shadows on the wall Illusions that
we build Afraid to leap, afraid to fall A
prophesy fulfilled The painted smiles a
masquerade To hide the fading spark A fragile
fortress we have made Against the growing dark,
but in the distance I can see A shimmer in the air,
a different kind of mystery A world beyond
compare Do you hear I whisper on the wind a melody
so clear? Oh, the true life gleams
Will you come back to where the true life gleams
and home is always near?
Through fractured prisms, light divides In
pair and sharp and bright Thou sandpats, where
fate presides Between the day and night Is I a
vision? Just a trace A trick of weary eyes Or is
there truly such a place Beneath those shifting
skies? Shelter from the endless rain A refuge
from the cold A story waiting to unfold, again to
be
told.
Do you hear it? A whisper on the wind, a melody so
clear Oh, the true light gleams
Will you come back to where the true light
gleams? And home is always near
Thanks for watching!